NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
{The Promise
{That Couldn't Be Kept
Kakashi-sensei...
Where's Sasuke?
Kakashi-san!
How is Uzumaki Naruto's condition?
He's okay.
What about Sasuke?
Where's Uchiha Sasuke?!
How are the other Genin?
Yes! By Hokage-sama's order
the first and second medical corps
have been dispatched...
The wounded from all areas have
already been gathered.
They were convoyed after
administering emergency treatment.
How are their conditions?
Yes! Nara Shikamaru has minor injuries...
Inuzuka Kiba has serious injuries
but it's not life-threatening.
Hyuga Neji and Akimichi Choji
are in serious condition...
At this point,
there's no telling what will happen.
Everyone...
The ingredients and
effects of the medicine
have been thoroughly researched.
Excellent...
Now bring the deer antler!
Yes ma'am!
How is he... nee-chan?
No walks for him for quite a while...
The muscles of his limbs
have been severely damaged.
You're a vet right, nee-chan?
Can't you somehow...?
It'll be okay.
It'll take time. But there's no threat
to his life so rest easy.
Walks for you are out of the question
for quite a while too!
Yeah, I know...
Intensive Care Unit 7
It'll soon be three hours...
Please take over.
All right!
Although we're making
this kid's hair into a conductor,
please don't mistake the cellular rate
of the deficient parts!
Right!
As for the Chakra control, handle it
as if we're threading a needle!
Understood!
Intensive Care Unit 6
There's no point in
you getting frustrated, right?
Missions come with sacrifice...
You took the mental training, right?
Training and actual battle
are different you know...
I know what missions are about...
And I thought I knew what
the Shinobi world is like.
I became a platoon leader
for the first time on this mission.
With that I understood...
I'm not cut out to be a Shinobi.
Surprisingly fragile... for a man.
This time...
The only thing I was able to do
as platoon leader...
was to believe in everyone.
I was naive...
I didn't have enough power...
It's all my fault!
Are you afraid of getting hurt?
Shikamaru...
Are you going to be argued down
by a girl and run away?
It's a drag...
I don't want to have arguments.
I'm not a woman.
Yeah... But you're not a man either.
You're just a coward!
Even if you quit being Shinobi
the missions will continue.
Someone has to do it.
Your comrades will just
be dispatched again...
under a different platoon leader.
And your comrades might die there.
But if at that time
you were the platoon leader...
your comrades might be saved
from that happening to them.
If you reflect on this time
make use of the experience and learn
you might be able to carry out missions
with more perfection.
If you really think your comrades
are important to you
before you think about running away...
think about becoming more exceptional
for the sake of your comrades!
That's what real comrades are
you coward!
Intensive Care Unit 6
He's okay now!
The antidote has stopped
the death of cells
caused by the side effects of the Pills.
You were a big help this time, Shikaku!
The Nara Clan's secret medicinal
preparation manual was very useful.
It must've been tough to
make something like that...
It's the result of day-to-day study.
Thanks...
Tsunade-sama!
Hyuga Neji...
His safety line has been secured.
And there's some information...
Hatake Kakashi and Uzumaki Naruto
have just now returned.
Although seriously injured
it seems it's not life-threatening.
Two, huh?
Shikamaru...
It seems the mission is a failure.
But everyone is alive!
That's the most important thing.
Next time for sure...
I'll carry out the mission perfectly!
Sasuke-kun... You're the chosen one.
Whatever... Just give me "power."
Even though the form is different
it's still Orochimaru-sama before your eyes.
If you don't want to die
use more care in how you talk.
Wh-What? This quality of Chakra...
Yes... My future is inside this kid...
Hidden Leaf Hospital
I'm going to where Orochimaru is!
Please... bring back Sasuke-kun!
I'll bring Sasuke back without fail!
I promise that on my life!
Oh... You were awake, huh?
Shikamaru!
I'm going on ahead to Choji!
What about you?
I'm going on ahead to...
Naruto and Sasuke-kun!
I see... So everyone's okay.
That's good.
Then Sasuke...
Yeah... he's gone.
Intensive Care Unit 6
Then I still can't see him...?
Yeah... But Tsunade-sama said that
he should regain consciousness soon.
Thank goodness...
It's really a great help that
Tsunade-sama returned
to the Leaf Village.
If she hadn't right about now
Choji would be...
The Fifth... Hokage-sama.
You've come to visit?
Information sure travels fast.
Sakura-chan...
Naruto...
I heard you suffered
quite a serious injury...
But you look well considering.
I'm sorry... Sakura-chan...
Why do you apologize?
Being you you probably
got reckless again, right?!
Jeez, you look like a mummy...
I'm sorry... I...
Hey... The weather's nice today.
So open the curtains.
Sakura-chan! I...
I'll keep my promise no matter what!
I promised on my life.
That's what I said so I...!
It's okay already, Naruto...
Sakura! He...
I always...
said that so... I...
I stick straight to what I say!
That's my Ninja Way!
Naruto...
Thanks Naruto...
I'll get right to healing this injury
and I've got to bring Sasuke back!
Wh-What was that?!
Per... Pervy Sage?!
Yo!
I've come today to tell you
something important.
From here on
as my official disciple,
I'll train you to become
a full-fledged Shinobi in three years.
Three years...?
I've received some credible information
from a certain source
concerning the "Akatsuki."
Akatsuki...
It seems that it will be
three or four years
before they come after you next.
I don't care about that!
Talking about stuff that's
so far down the road...
I don't have the time
to be doing slowpoke training!
What do you mean?
If I don't go after
Sasuke immediately
he might be killed by Orochimaru!
"Immortal" doesn't mean that
the flesh is being maintained as is.
Before his body decays
a strong and new flesh will be made
into a vessel for his soul.
It seems you've learned
of the true purpose
for Orochimaru seeking Sasuke...
Huh?! Then that means you also knew...?
I was looking into
Orochimaru's Immortality Jutsu.
It seems with that Jutsu
he can't reincarnate into
the next body for three years.
And unable to wait for Sasuke
he just recently reincarnated...
It'll be okay for three years from now...
There is time.
That's not a lie, is it?!
Not a lie, is it?!
Nope...
However...
Forget about Sasuke...
Sasuke went to Orochimaru
on his own accord.
No matter what you do
he won't change.
I've seen many Shinobi so I know...
Sasuke is the same kind
as Orochimaru.
If you're thinking about bringing him back
just forget it.
That's something an arrogant fool
would do!
He may be nothing to you
but he's my friend!
Would a friend hurt his comrade?!
Take a look at your current plight!
This is...!
Why? Why would you...?
We were called Sannin together...
Weren't we comrades
since we were kids?!
In every regard
you're a foolish guy, Jiraiya...
You lack thought
in everything you do.
That's why you didn't notice
what I was doing.
Can't you rethink it, Orochimaru?
Absurd!
How can you be so stupid?!
No matter how much I wanted it...
in the end there was no way
he would come back.
After the agony, all that's left was
my own powerlessness and regret.
I don't want you to go through
the same thing...
If you're going to go after Sasuke
then there'll be no training.
I'll get ANBU Black Ops to watch you
and depending on the case
prohibit you from leaving the village.
You're not just an ordinary kid...
You possess the Nine Tail Fox
that the Akatsuki is after!
This is serious.
I'll just have to do that...
if you're going to act on your own
without listening to what I say.
Eventually you're going to have to deal
with guys more troublesome
than Orochimaru.
Give up on Sasuke.
Sooner or later this was
going to happen.
Don't suffer anymore!
Forget and dismiss him.
It's not just Jutsu or power...
If you're a Shinobi develop eyes that
can make the right judgment.
And if you're going to live
as a Shinobi become wise.
If you remain a fool...
the reality is that it will be tough
living in this world.
Fine.
If that's what being wise is...
Then I'm fine being a fool for life!
Even if by myself
I'll create even more awesome Jutsu
and save Sasuke no matter what!
And and
I'll even kick the Akatsuki's butt!
If someone like you
were to do it alone...
the best you'd be able
to come up with
would be some
stupid erotic Jutsu anyway.
It might somehow work out
if you are a big fool and
not an ordinary fool...
Be prepared once
you're out of the hospital
you big fool.
See you then.
Roger!
— It's been seven years since...
— ...all the members gathered like this.
Since Orochimaru left
the organization.
That Orochimaru has gotten
the Sharingan.
Itachi... Your younger brother?
Don't get hasty. Yeah.
We'll kill Orochimaru eventually...
More importantly
there are only three years left.
Can everyone accomplish
the work required of them?
Huh?
Yes, our goal is...
to get everything
including the Nine Tail Fox in question!
hitotsu hitotsu omoidaseba
when I recalled the parts one by one,
subete wakatteita kigashite ita no ni
I felt as though I had understood everything
iroaseta kotoba wa
faded words
boku no sugu soba ni oite atta
which I kept so close to me
kotae no denai yoru to
speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
hitokira no nukumori to
and this distant yearning for you
haruka kanata no akogare to
I live,
tada sore dake wo
simply repeating this cycle
kurikaeshi boku wa ikite iru
held in my two hands
kono ryoute ni kakaete iru mono
a droplet of time
toki no shizuku
softly clutching forgotten memories
sotto nigirishimete wasureta kioku
lost words
nakushita kotoba
I'll keep these thoughts...
kono omoi wa
Sakura-chan's been weird all along
ever since Sasuke left.
I can't put it well
but she's gloomy or fretting
or something.
On top of that she says,
"This time I'll do my best on my own."
What the hell does that mean?
It's bugging me, it's bugging me!
This isn't the time for me
to be relaxing in the hospital!
Next episode:
"Infiltration Investigation?! A Super S-Class mission has Finally Arrived."